<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30DaysOfWellness</string>
    <string name="day1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="title1">Mindful Meditation</string>
    <string name="subtitle1">Engage in daily meditation to calm your mind, improve focus, and reduce stress. A few minutes each day can foster mental clarity and inner peace.</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="title2">Quality Sleep</string>
    <string name="subtitle2">Sleep is essential for physical and mental recovery. Prioritize 7–9 hours each night for enhanced energy, focus, and resilience</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="title3">Morning Stretching</string>
    <string name="subtitle3">Begin each day with gentle stretches. It increases flexibility, improves circulation, and prepares your body and mind for the day ahead.</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="title4">Balanced Nutrition</string>
    <string name="subtitle4">Fuel your body with a mix of proteins, fats, and carbs. A balanced diet supports mental clarity, energy, and immune function.</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="title5">Daily Gratitude</string>
    <string name="subtitle5">Reflect on what youre thankful for daily. Cultivating gratitude can enhance mood, improve mental health, and boost positivity.</string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="title6">Digital Detox</string>
    <string name="subtitle6">Take a break from screens for a set time daily. Disconnecting refreshes the mind, reduces stress, and improves sleep quality.</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="title7">Breathwork Practice</string>
    <string name="subtitle7">Simple breath exercises calm the nervous system and reduce stress. Practice deep breathing for a few minutes each day to promote relaxation.</string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="title8">Nature Walks</string>
    <string name="subtitle8">Spending time in nature relieves stress, enhances creativity, and boosts mental clarity. A short walk can have lasting effects.</string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="title9">Journaling</string>
    <string name="subtitle9">Write down your thoughts, goals, or challenges daily. Journaling promotes self-reflection, reduces stress, and enhances self-awareness.</string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="title10">Declutter for Calm</string>
    <string name="subtitle10">A tidy space fosters a clear mind. Set aside time to organize your space, reducing stress and boosting productivity.</string>

</resources>